flauntr.com 2012-01-30

# flauntR

Die englischsprachige Version dieses Dokuments ist die rechtlich allein bindende Version. In Kürze werden wir Ihnen zu Ihrer Information eine deutsche Übersetzung dieses Dokuments zur Verfügung stellen.

flauntR ("flauntR Inc.") is committed to protecting your privacy and recognizes that your privacy is important. The following privacy policy discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices from our website and our flauntR service. By using our website or our flauntR service, you agree to be bound by the terms of this policy.

 **Personal Information**

Personal information is information that is unique to you and includes your name, address, password, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, location information, product and service information, information on software downloads and updates, systems information, IP address, browser type, date and time of any request made to flauntR, content preferences, purchase information and credit card billing information. You may also be required to set up a user ID and password, which may be considered personal information. We may collect and store such personal information from you via our service. Because protecting your information is important to us, we do not sell any personal information to third parties. Some of the services that flauntR offers do not require you to provide any personal information. In order to provide certain services we may collect personal Information. When you send e-mail or other communication to flauntR, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. The information is stored on flauntR servers and is sent to and from such servers as part of routine product communications that enable software functionality

flauntR uses this information to:

a) Verify access rights to premium content, services or software (that might be introduced in the future).

b) Provide you with information about products, services, news and events.

c) Allow you to purchase and download products and services.

d) Provide you with advertising, promotions and special offers we feel you may be interested in based on information you provide to us. 

e) Provide you with personalised content, instructions and services. 

f) Calculate license reporting, billing, royalty payments and assessment of service levels. 

g) Understand on an aggregated basis how our products are used, traffic patterns and what types of content and services are most popular with users of our products and services. 

We may use independent contractors to provide services on our behalf. Such third parties may have access to your personal information in the course of providing services on our behalf. Such third parties will take commercially reasonable measures to keep your personal information safe, private and secure.

**Information Automatically Logged** ****

Our systems may automatically log certain non-personal information such as your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, to help administer our service or to perform analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services

**Email Newsletter** ****

You will be required to submit your e-mail address during the registration process. This information is used solely by flauntR and will not be sold to any third party. We will use this information to send weekly newsletters about product updates and new releases. You may always opt out of receiving our newsletters.

**Security** ****

We will take commercially reasonable measures in providing secure transmission of your personal information before it is transferred across the Internet from your personal computer to our servers and in securing such personal information stored on our systems. However, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet and that there is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of personal information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

We restrict access to personal information to flauntR employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations.

 **Cookies/Identifier files**

flauntR uses cookies or other identifier files in connection with the use of flauntR services. These are small bits of data, which includes an unique identifier that is sent to your computer+rsquo;s browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use these files to store information about your visits. We also use these files to enhance your experience as you visit the website.

If you choose to delete or disable your these files some of the features and services of flauntR may not function properly.

**Information Sharing**

We offer services in connection with other websites. This site may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These sites have their own policies regarding privacy, we encourage you to read their privacy policy. We bear no responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for your convenience and information.

If flauntR becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Restriction on the basis of age**

If you are residing in a jurisdiction which restricts the use of internet-based applications according to age, or which restricts the ability to enter into agreements such as this agreement according to age and you are in such a jurisdiction and under such age limit, you may not enter into this agreement and use the flauntR software. By entering into this agreement you explicitly state that you have verified in your own jurisdiction that your use of the flauntR software is allowed.

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail or postal mail as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to anyone who is under the age limit to use internet based applications

**Changes to this policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time as we continue to offer more flauntR services. In the event of any material or substantial change in the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, flauntR may notify you via e-mail, and/or by posting an announcement of the changes on the service. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep a prior version of the policy in an archive for your review. You can find the latest version of this Privacy Policy at the flauntR website.

**Contacting flaunt R**

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account information. You are responsible for all activities that occur in your account and you agree to notify flauntR immediately of any unauthorized account use. flauntR is in no way responsible for any loss that you may incur as a result of any unauthorized use of your user account and password. 

If, for any reason, you are concerned with the way that we may be using your personal information, you would like to request that we cease using your personal information altogether, or you wish to file a complaint, you may contact us via our website.
